This is what Guru Mahārāj says
Questo è quello che dice Guru Mahārāj
about taking a stand with spiritual common sense.
a proposito del prendere posizione con buon senso spirituale.
I can sit here, we can quote so many scriptures, verses, etc.
Posso sedermi qui, citare molte scritture, versi, ecc.
but also just use your common sense too.
ma anche semplicemente usare il buon senso.
[Is God Male, Female, or Both?]
[Dio è Maschio, Femmina o Entrambi?]
There’s another liker as we speak.
C'é un altro sostenitore mentre parliamo.
learn from it!
traetene insegnamento!
It must be there in the original.
Deve esserci nell'originale.
This is the driving principle of existence,
Questo è il principio guida dell'esistenza,
So, for the most part, in religion there’s a male God,
dunque, il più delle volte, nella religione c'è un Dio maschile,
and the feminine aspect is under-served, under-represented,
e l'aspetto femminile è meno considerato, meno rappresentato,
to put it mildly.
per usare un eufemismo.
Then, what do people think to compensate for that?
Allora, cosa pensa la gente per compensare?
“Yes! So, we worship the Goddess!”
«Si! allora noi adoriamo la Dea!»
Just to go in the other direction.
Giusto per andare nell'altra direzione.
But the only fully balanced complete expression of Divinity is in Bhagavān—
Ma l'unica espressione pienamente equilibrata e completa del divino è in Bhagavān,
meaning: Śakti−Śaktimān;
ossia : Śakti−Śaktimān;
feminine aspect and male aspect;
l'aspetto femminile e l'aspetto maschile;
the Supreme Female and the Supreme Male.
il Supremo Femminile e il Supremo Maschile.